<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>I use technology to create and restore balance</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://blog.codeparity.com/</id><updated>2022-02-14T13:31:00+05:30</updated><subtitle>A personal views by Ashish Tanwar aka Codeparity</subtitle><entry><title>Second Call-out to Google Cloud Management</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/my-google-mail-2.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-01-10T01:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-02-14T13:31:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Codeparity aka Ashish Tanwar</name></author><id>tag:blog.codeparity.com,2022-01-10:/my-google-mail-2.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;Second callout to the scared &lt;em&gt;hasbeens&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is the second of the mails which i sent to the whole India&amp;nbsp;team.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The gang of &lt;em&gt;hasbeens&lt;/em&gt; got visibly enraged after mail 1. A decent last working date was too much to ask for, warnings and notices followed. It did not&amp;nbsp;matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jan 10, 2022, 1:00 &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear&amp;nbsp;All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just submitted my resignation. I don&amp;#8217;t care if they compensate, or fine me. I am gone from today.
Apologies to my colleagues, I waited to make sure I passed the baton to the right set of people, I think you will do well. I am walking out thinking that I have not let you down as a colleague or as a person or what is expected out of a commodity &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NI&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;em&gt;Needs Improvement&lt;/em&gt;) rated&amp;nbsp;L6.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that you would find courage to speak when leadership is just playing musical chairs within themselves, while the people who actually do the work wait for a year to get migrated or find better options outside. This is harmful to Gargle, and the country as a whole. This &amp;#8220;rebellion&amp;#8221; is my expression of solving for a bigger cause than myself - Parity should be restored after this, and you need to leverage this chance to restore culture, logic in this team. I am making sure that this cannot be curbed at a regional level.
Do trust &lt;em&gt;internalUselessLink1&lt;/em&gt; - you may end up succeeding like me and believe me - the biggest challenge for me was accepting the reality of it, keeping my sanity at work and personal life. My former buddy knows all about&amp;nbsp;it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will speak from a position of strength when you next hear from me. I have better things to do, dealing with goinmul coterie is there, but like at priority 5. It&amp;#8217;s Gargle&amp;#8217;s fault, not mine to&amp;nbsp;correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep in touch - linkedin, whatsapp etc are good. TeamBlind.com is&amp;nbsp;excellent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To my Managers(s) and &lt;em&gt;uselessops&lt;/em&gt; team:
I want to acknowledge my failure to adhere to &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PIP&lt;/span&gt; since I was rated &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NI&lt;/span&gt; in October&amp;nbsp;2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last day is 26 April 2022, the same day my second tranche of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GSU&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s mature. I hope to have no further negotiations or communication on&amp;nbsp;this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In spirit of accountability, few developments-
&lt;em&gt;Bill&lt;/em&gt; for &lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor2&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Opportunity1&lt;/em&gt; has been raised - 100% confident that you will win this.
&lt;em&gt;CustomerDifficult1&lt;/em&gt; is executing an &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IIOT&lt;/span&gt; opportunity with us, this needs holdhanding as its a pure &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IIOT&lt;/span&gt; win with an incumbent partner.
&lt;em&gt;PartnerGood1&lt;/em&gt; is all slated to sign up as exclusive or optimal partner for Gargle Cloud&amp;#8217; &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IIOT&lt;/span&gt; practice - across the whole subcontinent. I was able to convince them to model their solution on Gargle Cloud&amp;#8217;s &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IIOT&lt;/span&gt; reference architecture - did this in 2 hours - 2/3 meetings. (&lt;em&gt;PartnerGood1&lt;/em&gt;  team is a good, considering the low &lt;span class="caps"&gt;POC&lt;/span&gt; cost and their hunger to succeed.)
&amp;#64;my &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NI&lt;/span&gt; rating manager and leadership in general - I just gave you the biggest callout of your life. My advise&amp;nbsp;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Respect &lt;em&gt;InternalSurvey&lt;/em&gt; results.
Do what you are hired to do - geo strat based deal making should be the best lever.
If people are leaving&amp;#8230;..linkedin leadership shares - you need to&amp;nbsp;act.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#8217;s all there in the motto - Dinosaurs&amp;nbsp;etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for the ride and fuelling me with enough contempt to fire for next few years, thought I was burnt&amp;nbsp;out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ashish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ps:
To the people who still like me - I am starting a new venture, will keep you posted via linkedin/codeparity.com(its on Gargle Workspace), or just reach out. I am on a quest to define IndianNess - We were and are quite capable of being sustainable. I have it planned like a suspense novel - It would be worth it - some shawshank stuff coming up - all from an underdog who came from nowhere and is absolutely expected to get burned (0% employment probability after&amp;nbsp;this)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear manager(s) - This is what i told you about - &amp;#8220;Joker&amp;#8221; mode : a guy who has a bad day and turns the values of an institution against it, I hope you get it&amp;#8230;.and yes i have thought through - I &amp;#8220;know&amp;#8221;&amp;nbsp;this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal message to the leader who likes &amp;#8220;imagine dragons&amp;#8221; and &amp;#8220;pink floyd&amp;#8221; - poetic justice coming right up? &amp;#8230;. &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_JF8oSxXtM"&gt;Motorhead&amp;nbsp;Fan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Googleness - This is the last bit of my duty to Gargle - I will not sue you - someone else may, gears are turning, and it would be beautiful - the hundreds of hours i wasted in explaining and justifying myself - it is going to multiply on you. Time/efficiency is the real currency, not $$$ or account&amp;nbsp;plans.&lt;/p&gt;
</content><category term="Google"></category><category term="Google"></category><category term="Cloud"></category><category term="Performance"></category><category term="Fairness"></category><category term="ethics"></category></entry></feed>