<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Tech for balance</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://blog.codeparity.com/</id><updated>2022-05-17T16:02:31+05:30</updated><subtitle>Codeparity Blog</subtitle><entry><title>Status check - 17 May 2022</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/status-update-may2022.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-05-17T15:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-17T15:49:02+05:30</updated><author><name>Codeparity aka Ashish Tanwar</name></author><id>tag:blog.codeparity.com,2022-05-17:/status-update-may2022.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;last 4 months&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wanted to write this post - started to get a lot of check-ins from people wondering what I have been upto. Most are curious about my mentally health and wellbeing….having chosen to own my reclusive nature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professionally, I am on schedule. Repeating past mistakes is a pattern of insanity, quite aware of the usual. Some things become apparent as you age, for me these have been my priorities in the last 4 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="getting-my-strength-back"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Getting my strength back&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Physical fitness is an absolute necessity in today’s environment. Having a family is a duty, and depending on law enforcement for their safety is absolute stupidity. Blessed to have the best Chief Minister of the country - Yogi Adityanath - that  should not become a reason to become complacent. Law, Police in India are the most pathetic administrative public services in the world…something which won't change in the current scheme of things. Would reason in a separate post.
Hand is better than before now, and the mind/body balance has been restored, though a bigger challenge of creating a sustainable routine remains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="extending-my-reach"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Extending my reach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One’s opportunity and success are highly influenced by the people around them. Being born in  the middle class, I am very much affected by this  bubble or sphere of influence. The last time I launched Codeparity, I counted on the goodwill of the people around me - which did not work out at all. I ended up wasting weeks. Won't happen this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="realigning-priorities-their-order"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Realigning, priorities their order&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I left Google in weird circumstances. No matter how I want to ignore this …. One needs time to counter for self bias and get a hold on your reality. Time is invaluable in this exercise. Being an engineer at heart, execution comes easy to me, and that has not really helped things.
With all that done, I am back in the professional sphere again - not as a jobber but as an entrepreneur and investor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you out there. Please follow me on twitter : &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://twitter.com/ashishtanwar"&gt;ashishtanwar&lt;/a&gt;, the wokeness of platforms like linkedin and twitter sickens me, and this is one of the few social/tech issues i would work on in coming months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="life"></category><category term="life"></category><category term="India"></category><category term="Career"></category><category term="Priorities"></category><category term="Update"></category></entry><entry><title>Applying Maslow's triangle</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/maslaw-needs-heirrarchy-1.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-03-01T01:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-17T16:02:31+05:30</updated><author><name>Codeparity aka Ashish Tanwar</name></author><id>tag:blog.codeparity.com,2022-03-01:/maslaw-needs-heirrarchy-1.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;Understanding Maslow's hierarchy of needs&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maslow's hierarchy of needs can be useful in understanding an individual, community or a country&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content><category term="life"></category><category term="psychology"></category><category term="analysis"></category><category term="maslow"></category></entry><entry><title>Follow up to Google Cloud Management</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/my-google-mail-2.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-01-10T01:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-02-14T13:31:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Codeparity aka Ashish Tanwar</name></author><id>tag:blog.codeparity.com,2022-01-10:/my-google-mail-2.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;Second callout to the scared &lt;em&gt;hasbeens&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is the second and final mail which i sent to the whole India team.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The gang of &lt;em&gt;hasbeens&lt;/em&gt; got visibly enraged after mail 1. A decent last working date was too much to ask for, warnings and notices followed. It did not matter. This one is nicer though.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jan 10, 2022, 1:00 PM&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear All,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just submitted my resignation. I don't care if they compensate, or fine me. I am gone from today.
Apologies to my colleagues, I waited to make sure I passed the baton to the right set of people, I think you will do well. I am walking out thinking that I have not let you down as a colleague or as a person or what is expected out of a commodity NI(&lt;em&gt;Needs Improvement&lt;/em&gt;) rated L6.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope that you would find courage to speak when leadership is just playing musical chairs within themselves, while the people who actually do the work wait for a year to get migrated or find better options outside. This is harmful to Gargle, and the country as a whole. This &amp;quot;rebellion&amp;quot; is my expression of solving for a bigger cause than myself - Parity should be restored after this, and you need to leverage this chance to restore culture, logic in this team. I am making sure that this cannot be curbed at a regional level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do trust &lt;em&gt;internalUselessLink1&lt;/em&gt; - you may end up succeeding like me and believe me - the biggest challenge for me was accepting the reality of it, keeping my sanity at work and personal life. My former buddy knows all about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will speak from a position of strength when you next hear from me. I have better things to do, dealing with goinmul coterie is there, but like at priority 5. It's Gargle's fault, not mine to correct.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep in touch - linkedin, whatsapp etc are good. TeamBlind.com is excellent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To my Managers(s) and &lt;em&gt;uselessops&lt;/em&gt; team:
I want to acknowledge my failure to adhere to PIP since I was rated NI in October 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last day is 26 April 2022, the same day my second tranche of GSU's mature. I hope to have no further negotiations or communication on this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In spirit of accountability, few developments-&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bill&lt;/em&gt; for &lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor2&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Opportunity1&lt;/em&gt; has been raised - 100% confident that you will win this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CustomerDifficult1&lt;/em&gt; is executing an IIOT opportunity with us, this needs holdhanding as its a pure IIOT win with an incumbent partner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PartnerGood1&lt;/em&gt; is all slated to sign up as exclusive or optimal partner for Gargle Cloud' IIOT practice - across the whole subcontinent. I was able to convince them to model their solution on Gargle Cloud's IIOT reference architecture - did this in 2 hours - 2/3 meetings. (&lt;em&gt;PartnerGood1&lt;/em&gt;  team is a good, considering the low POC cost and their hunger to succeed.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;#64;my NI rating manager and leadership in general - I just gave you the biggest callout of your life. My advise :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Respect &lt;em&gt;InternalSurvey&lt;/em&gt; results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do what you are hired to do - geo strat based deal making should be the best lever.
If people are leaving.....linkedin leadership shares - you need to act.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's all there in the motto - Dinosaurs etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for the ride and fuelling me with enough contempt to fire for next few years, thought I was burnt out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ashish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To the people who still like me - I am starting a new venture, will keep you posted via linkedin/codeparity.com(its on Gargle Workspace), or just reach out. I am on a quest to define IndianNess - We were and are quite capable of being sustainable. I have it planned like a suspense novel - It would be worth it - some shawshank stuff coming up - all from an underdog who came from nowhere and is absolutely expected to get burned (0% employment probability after this)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dear manager(s) - This is what i told you about - &amp;quot;Joker&amp;quot; mode : a guy who has a bad day and turns the values of an institution against it, I hope you get it....and yes i have thought through - I &amp;quot;know&amp;quot; this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personal message to the leader who likes &amp;quot;imagine dragons&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;pink floyd&amp;quot; - poetic justice coming right up? .... &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F_JF8oSxXtM"&gt;Motorhead Fan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On Googleness - This is the last bit of my duty to Gargle - I will not sue you - someone else may, gears are turning, and it would be beautiful - the hundreds of hours i wasted in explaining and justifying myself - it is going to multiply on you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time/efficiency is the real currency, not $$$ or account plans.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</content><category term="Google"></category><category term="Google"></category><category term="Cloud"></category><category term="Performance"></category><category term="Fairness"></category><category term="ethics"></category></entry><entry><title>Initial call-out to Google Cloud</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/my-google-mail-1.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-01-07T16:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-02-14T11:23:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Codeparity aka Ashish Tanwar</name></author><id>tag:blog.codeparity.com,2022-01-07:/my-google-mail-1.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;An overview of what happened at Google during my last days&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is the first of the mails which i sent to the whole India team.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scared &lt;em&gt;hasbeens&lt;/em&gt; in the Google Cloud India management did not have guts to reply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It caused quite a stir- got innumerable messages of support and kudos for calling out these &lt;em&gt;hasbeens&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is quite boring, but if you have wandered off to here, i am guessing this appeals to you. So, enough words, here you go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi Team,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This may be my last allowed communication here, doing this because I really doubt the reality or rather applicability of those values and culture (LT, its called SRE, something we preach) in our team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now : I alleged harassment, discrimination, bias and all bad things after i was rated NI by enligtened and respected DimwitManager1 with firm endorsement from L/T . I appealed and lost.
I will leave the judgment to you...needy, delusional, whatever.....i am gone anyways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I have you hooked, so I will make it absolutely worth your time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First 3 months:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
My CV is on my MOMA profile, it won't take a genius to notice that I should be in the D/N or AppMod team. I was ACE and PCA certified even before google interviewed me. Thats something which &lt;em&gt;HasbeenLeader1&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;DimwitManager1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3&lt;/em&gt; have &amp;quot;conveniently&amp;quot; chose to ignore and plead the third amendment - &amp;quot;Management reserves the right to allocate based on priority of business..blah blah&amp;quot;.
Anyways, I don't have either the equipment or work allocated to me, I used this time to learn about the culture ( proof - see my moma batch, and my annoying memegens). One thing became evident - we survive by logic and foresightedness.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;HasbeenLeader1&lt;/em&gt;  and &lt;em&gt;PeerChor1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
I am allocated BFSI - no rhyme or reason. I am starving for work, put under immense pressure by &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;PeerChor1&lt;/em&gt;, combined with &lt;em&gt;HasbeenLeader1&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3&lt;/em&gt;. eg - cold calling, pursuing leads via partners, being humiliated for not being good at it. These &amp;quot;leaders&amp;quot; force me to use stolen artifacts from orakle to create their elusive &amp;quot;account plan&amp;quot;. I resist, and get crucified for it. &lt;em&gt;PeerChor1&lt;/em&gt; is OOO to never return. I am constantly humiliated by &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; who is openly targeting me now. Focused on learning about BFSI, I created a solution based on my 3 months &amp;quot;expertise&amp;quot; on BFSI, on boarding customers and seeking new opportunities.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start of 2021 :&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I ask &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt;  to allocate me D/N &lt;em&gt;D/N - basically customers who code&lt;/em&gt;. I wasn't given. I was given CPG and an opportunity to help every FSR who needed help. &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt;  was shortly out of action, so I took this as a challenge to max out and put my skills to test. Here is the somewhat comprehensive list of accounts on which I have worked, Remember, even auto, iot accounts were denied to me. All i got was &lt;em&gt;CustomerAutoMajor&lt;/em&gt; as the &amp;quot;Biggest Opportunity&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unacknowledged Impact in BFSI:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I even got a deal closed - Voice translation API for &lt;em&gt;CustomerBigNationalizedBank&lt;/em&gt;. I even went to interview potential partners to realize the deal - &lt;em&gt;ITMajor1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ITMajor2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ITMajor3&lt;/em&gt; - finally selected and on-boarded by me - &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood1&lt;/em&gt; can attest.
I never got even a mention in the pipe I predominantly created and realized when &lt;em&gt;PeerChor1&lt;/em&gt; was out of action. Ask &lt;em&gt;PeerOpportunist1&lt;/em&gt; - If i did not go over and beyond to onboard him. All I ever got was 2 shadow sessions and a reminder in every team meeting that I am not good enough. I choose to focus on the skills I lacked - patience, communication and anxiety in big meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, this is the time when the team was falling sick, left and right. I am helping &lt;em&gt;PeerOpportunist2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;PeerLiarUnskilled&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood3&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerScared&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood4&lt;/em&gt; and doing ########## with &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGoodBuddy&lt;/em&gt;, also trying to fill in for anyone that is feeling unwell. Except for 2 contentious meetings of probably 200+ senior personnel I communicated with, these meetings went well - something that I believe none of my FSRs can deny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contentious Meet 1 - Mr CIO (not sure) &lt;em&gt;CustomerStupid&lt;/em&gt;/&lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor1&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rude person. Immensely lacks manners, logic or value. I was insulted initially by title, then by experience, by skill, by values and finally by &amp;quot;Indianness&amp;quot;. That was the last straw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
Trivia/Shameless self boasting : Not many people can claim to have proven a crucial contribution to development of our country'&lt;em&gt;############ ######&lt;/em&gt;. Yes I am now proud that my code runs there....and it is still being used, reused and appreciated.
Snide comment : I know embedded, micro-controller, electronics, mobile apps, now cloud. When I say know - I have and can build them from scratch - from a chip supplier to programming or creating the toolchain, apps and finally selling it to end customers. My end customers have been &lt;em&gt;PastBigCustomer&lt;/em&gt;, then &lt;em&gt;GovtOfficial1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;GovtOfficial2&lt;/em&gt; - &lt;em&gt;GovtBody1&lt;/em&gt;, Heads of Police, &lt;em&gt;GovtSecurityBody&lt;/em&gt; etc, &lt;em&gt;GovtOfficia3&lt;/em&gt;, heads of state security to mobile manufactures like &lt;em&gt;OEM1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;OEM2&lt;/em&gt; etc. I influenced the requirements by &lt;em&gt;GovtBody1&lt;/em&gt; on mobile operators that now have made it mandatory for them to provide at least 30 mtr of geolocation accuracy for tracking. Influenced and made them aware that telecom providers are not providing &amp;quot;real time&amp;quot; tracking as they are hiding the X interface - GSM ref.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways - i ended up telling the customer - &lt;em&gt;&amp;quot;Sir, I will send you the link to the entire portfolio, Please do call me if you need us. I have more intelligent customers who actually need me&amp;quot;.&lt;/em&gt; I know....this was after an hour of humiliation being labeled a data chor (Gargle and I were betraying the country for working there).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;10 seconds of silence. He could not believe a &amp;quot;sales&amp;quot; ka sirf customer engineer can tell the factual truth to an &amp;quot;innocent&amp;quot; person. Then he starts selling &lt;em&gt;AyurvedaMajor1&lt;/em&gt; to us - giving us requirements and all. I am really running late to an yum IOT opportunity - &lt;em&gt;CustomerBigMeterCompany&lt;/em&gt;.
I wanted to calm my nerves before that, so this time i am genuinely asking Dear Customer to let me go, he ends up giving us requirements for his immediate &amp;quot;$$$$$$ requirement&amp;quot; -  GargleCloud's value proposition. FSR and I sync up after call, HI5 and conclude that this was an amazing meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All pumped up, we have a great opening meeting at &lt;em&gt;CustomerBigMeterCompany&lt;/em&gt; again. Good, hard week....this is Friday....finally a weekend when I can be proud of the week I had. 10 PM, unusual chat ping from FSR. He/She inquires whether we can talk.
Trivia : I am a father of one 5 year old human, 2 very loving yet annoying dogs and a pseudo father of 40 - 60 street dogs. After 6 PM, my highly stressed wife had given me a notice - money is not enough, you are needed. There was proof to that - my son was not speaking Hindi even at 4 years. Corona time....we all struggle with this. I am barely giving time to anyone. My mom passes - i am in Noida, she lives in our old permanent home at rohini, Delhi. I am guilty of not making enough time for her, and probably causing her death....i am still coping up with this guilt.
The reason I am telling you this is to simply imply that 7PM to 11Pm is an absolute must for me - I have to take over from my wife who is highly stressed being in the final leg of her Phd. She is doing well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, Mr &lt;em&gt;CustomerStupid&lt;/em&gt;/&lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor1&lt;/em&gt; , probably after getting drunk at 10PM on Friday, gave a call to former FSR and apparently threatened to file a police complaint. I was all for it - It was on web conf, and I thought the version is exaggerated, I tell the FSR to sleep it off, after i finally get done with my day which ends at 11 PM normally - this includes making food for my street dogs - being hated for it, and recently being attacked for it. I hope you saw the video. This is after my moms's demise on 28 April, coincidentally the week when &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; joins back from vacation. He is trying to do his thing again - perpetrating general hate against me - my lack of patience, skills and after this meeting 1, even my character for taking a call late at night from a female FSR.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Made up Contentious meeting 2 : &lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor2&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PeerLyingUnskilled&lt;/em&gt; lead a disaster of a meeting. &lt;em&gt;PeerLyingUnskilled&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerSenior1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;PeerAnalyticsSpecialist&lt;/em&gt; are speakers in the meet, i was just a mute spectator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The meeting goes horribly wrong, time management, content - everything. &lt;em&gt;PeerLyingUnskilled&lt;/em&gt; is panicking and trying to convince me to put blame on &lt;em&gt;PeerAnalyticsSpecialist&lt;/em&gt;, who is a nagler &lt;em&gt;(a new joinee)&lt;/em&gt; at this point. I refuse to intervene and tell her to think about it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BTW, its the same account where I got CIO's approval for ######## assessment just a few days back. This is the only reason why we have an edge over competition, and why &lt;em&gt;PartnerImplementor1&lt;/em&gt; has really partnered with us in this account - a fact that LT conveniently forgets to consider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;PeerLyingUnskilled&lt;/em&gt; tells the management that I screwed the meeting up (I was not even allowed to speak in the meet - &lt;em&gt;CoworkerSenior1&lt;/em&gt;/&lt;em&gt;PeerAnalyticsSpecialist&lt;/em&gt; can validate).
I am never asked to clarify or asked what went wrong. (L/T - Blamelessness and RCA is part of SRE)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the same time period when I am dealing or rather coping up with implications of my Mothers' death - the ugly material part of it. Summary - I ended up abandoning all my savings, investments, property to focus on work and move on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things are going well in other accounts - All the other FSRs seem happy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;18 June, when things were at their decisive time, I was attacked by 3 crazy but quite well built people with Iron rods for 15 mins.
I got my first entitlement of being a gargler - got the days off while I dealt with these all pending issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August 2021&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In last week of August, I &lt;em&gt;soft&lt;/em&gt; joined back with a barely functioning hand, trying to handle the piled up work. Got exceptional support from &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood2&lt;/em&gt;, he created a few deals while I was gone.
I had lost 3 absolutely winnable dials - the FSRs don't call me out of respect or sheer self promotional reasons. There were many wins, I was never credited.
Meanwhile, &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; is going and &lt;em&gt;DimwitManager1&lt;/em&gt; joins, I request &lt;em&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3&lt;/em&gt; to give a true assessment of my progress to enlightened &lt;em&gt;DimwitManager1&lt;/em&gt;, but I am &amp;quot;hinted informally&amp;quot; that I am not meeting the OKRs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I give a very detailed and logical lay of the land - progress, key developments and the general good feedback I was getting from customers, partners and even my peers. I am told to prepare 10 account plans as per OKRs, I inform him that these are &amp;quot;traditional enterprise accounts' ', their tech stack cannot be deduced by nmap or any other open source intelligence tools. I inform him about my participation in DevJam and the other bits where I have been helping, but he doesn't listen. I tell him about my experience in D/N and my love for gaming and IIOT - power sector etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power accounts are taken away from me, the regional IIOT lead is a guy who doesn't even know &amp;quot;IT/OT&amp;quot;. I am left with &lt;em&gt;PeerLiarUnskilled&lt;/em&gt; who has been lying and claiming credit for all my work even till day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was given NI &lt;em&gt;Needs Improvement&lt;/em&gt;, and contested that, just lost that appeal. My accounts have been ignored - &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR3&lt;/em&gt; are all big accounts which need a higher level handshake - all of them have been ignored by my local leadership just to continue painting me as incompetent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that is my journey till day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My customers seem to like me more than my management, and they are easier to work with too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor2&lt;/em&gt; deal is on because I pivoted the deal. ################### which finally put the deal on track. LT is going to continue sabotaging my deals in BD- &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR2&lt;/em&gt;, and recently &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR3&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not a likable person by any means, if you have seen me in meets -  I give it all, and I believe thats what matters - being there for your colleagues and picking up the right priorities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet i am labelled incompetent for simply refusing to &amp;quot;dance&amp;quot; as per standards set by luminaries like &lt;em&gt;DimwitManager1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy new year!...I am going to make sure that mine makes me grow and evolve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the best, dealing with all this - I am going to do what I do best - stand up to the bully no matter who and how big they are, and it may get worse....I am prepared for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why it all happened, is something which is going to unravel in next few months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ashish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glossary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HasbeenLeader1 : India Head, my skip level, to his credit, he tried a lot to sound smart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ManagerDimwit1 : My current manager, rattu totta, His extreme loyalty to his Orakle breathren would put a Dogs' loyalty to shame - Amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ManagerDumbass2 : The last manager, who is sucking up in CanaDDa now, he was tasked with &amp;quot;taming&amp;quot; me. Look where we are :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3 : A sidey manager who would provide his useless gyan everywhere. Despite sucking for longer than anyone else and not getting anywhere, he seems optimistic.
moma patch : our internal page&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PeerChor : The guy who stole Orakle internal documents and forced me to use them. Part of orakle coterie of of HasbeenLeader1, ManagerIwantToMatter3 and probably ManagerDimwit1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PS : About Macros used,  i may choose to replace these in future with Real Names and Links :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#### : Readcted Stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
</content><category term="Google"></category><category term="Google"></category><category term="Cloud"></category><category term="Performance"></category><category term="Fairness"></category><category term="ethics"></category></entry></feed>