<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Codeparity Blog - random thoughts about tech, life and anything interesting - Google</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/feeds/google.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://blog.codeparity.com/</id><updated>2022-02-14T11:23:00+05:30</updated><entry><title>Initial Callout to Google Cloud Management</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/my-google-mail-1.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-01-07T16:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-02-14T11:23:00+05:30</updated><author><name>Codeparity</name></author><id>tag:blog.codeparity.com,2022-01-07:/my-google-mail-1.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;An overview of what happened at Google during my last&amp;nbsp;days&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;div class="section" id="this-is-the-first-of-mails-which-i-sent-to-the-whole-india-team"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;This is the first of mails which i sent to the whole India&amp;nbsp;team.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scared hasbeens in the management did not have guys to reply.
It caused quite a stir- got innumerable messages of support and kudos for calling out these&amp;nbsp;hasbeens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi&amp;nbsp;Team,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This may be my last allowed communication here, doing this because I really doubt the reality or rather applicability of those values and culture (&lt;span class="caps"&gt;LT&lt;/span&gt;, its called &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SRE&lt;/span&gt;, something we preach) in our&amp;nbsp;team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now : I alleged harassment, discrimination, bias and all bad things after i was rated &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NI&lt;/span&gt; by enligtened and respected DimwitManager1 with firm endorsement from L/T . I appealed and lost.
I will leave the judgment to you&amp;#8230;needy, delusional, whatever&amp;#8230;..i am gone&amp;nbsp;anyways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I have you hooked, so I will make it absolutely worth your&amp;nbsp;time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First 3 months:
My &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CV&lt;/span&gt; is on my &lt;span class="caps"&gt;MOMA&lt;/span&gt; profile, it won&amp;#8217;t take a genius to notice that I should be in the D/N or AppMod team. I was &lt;span class="caps"&gt;ACE&lt;/span&gt; and &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PCA&lt;/span&gt; certified even before google interviewed me. Thats something which &lt;em&gt;HasbeenLeader1&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;DimwitManager1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3&lt;/em&gt; have &amp;#8220;conveniently&amp;#8221; chose to ignore and plead the third amendment - &amp;#8220;Management reserves the right to allocate based on priority of business..blah blah&amp;#8221;.
Anyways, I don&amp;#8217;t have either the equipment or work allocated to me, I used this time to learn about the culture ( proof - see my moma batch, and my annoying memegens). One thing became evident - we survive by logic and&amp;nbsp;foresightedness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enter &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;HasbeenLeader1&lt;/em&gt;  and &lt;em&gt;PeerChor1&lt;/em&gt;,.
I am allocated &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BFSI&lt;/span&gt; - no rhyme or reason. I am starving for work, put under immense pressure by &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;PeerChor1&lt;/em&gt;, combined with &lt;em&gt;HasbeenLeader1&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3&lt;/em&gt;. eg - cold calling, pursuing leads via partners, being humiliated for not being good at it. These &amp;#8220;leaders&amp;#8221; force me to use stolen artifacts from orakle to create their elusive &amp;#8220;account plan&amp;#8221;. I resist, and get crucified for it. &lt;em&gt;PeerChor1&lt;/em&gt; is &lt;span class="caps"&gt;OOO&lt;/span&gt; to never return. I am constantly humiliated by &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; who is openly targeting me now. Focused on learning about &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BFSI&lt;/span&gt;, I created a solution based on my 3 months &amp;#8220;expertise&amp;#8221; on &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BFSI&lt;/span&gt;, on boarding customers and seeking new&amp;nbsp;opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start of 2021 :
I ask &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt;  to allocate me D/N &lt;em&gt;D/N - basically customers who code&lt;/em&gt;. I wasn&amp;#8217;t given. I was given &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CPG&lt;/span&gt; and an opportunity to help every &lt;span class="caps"&gt;FSR&lt;/span&gt; who needed help. &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt;  was shortly out of action, so I took this as a challenge to max out and put my skills to test. Here is the somewhat comprehensive list of accounts on which I have worked, Remember, even auto, iot accounts were denied to me. All i got was &lt;em&gt;CustomerAutoMajor&lt;/em&gt; as the &amp;#8220;Biggest&amp;nbsp;Opportunity&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unacknowledged Impact in &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BFSI&lt;/span&gt;:
I even got a deal closed - Voice translation &lt;span class="caps"&gt;API&lt;/span&gt; for &lt;em&gt;CustomerBigNationalizedBank&lt;/em&gt;. I even went to interview potential partners to realize the deal - &lt;em&gt;ITMajor1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ITMajor2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ITMajor3&lt;/em&gt; - finally selected and on-boarded by me - &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood1&lt;/em&gt; can attest.
I never got even a mention in the pipe I predominantly created and realized when &lt;em&gt;PeerChor1&lt;/em&gt; was out of action. Ask &lt;em&gt;PeerOpportunist1&lt;/em&gt; - If i did not go over and beyond to onboard him. All I ever got was 2 shadow sessions and a reminder in every team meeting that I am not good enough. I choose to focus on the skills I lacked - patience, communication and anxiety in big&amp;nbsp;meetings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, this is the time when the team was falling sick, left and right. I am helping &lt;em&gt;PeerOpportunist2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;PeerLiarUnskilled&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood3&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerScared&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood4&lt;/em&gt; and doing ########## with &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGoodBuddy&lt;/em&gt;, also trying to fill in for anyone that is feeling unwell. Except for 2 contentious meetings of probably 200+ senior personnel I communicated with, these meetings went well - something that I believe none of my FSRs can&amp;nbsp;deny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contentious Meet 1 - Mr &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CIO&lt;/span&gt; (not sure) &lt;em&gt;CustomerStupid&lt;/em&gt;/&lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor1&lt;/em&gt;.
Rude person. Immensely lacks manners, logic or value. I was insulted initially by title, then by experience, by skill, by values and finally by &amp;#8220;Indianness&amp;#8221;. That was the last&amp;nbsp;straw.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Trivia/Shameless self boasting : Not many people can claim to have proven a crucial contribution to development of our country&amp;#8217;&lt;em&gt;############ ######&lt;/em&gt;. Yes I am now proud that my code runs there&amp;#8230;.and it is still being used, reused and appreciated.
Snide comment : I know embedded, micro-controller, electronics, mobile apps, now cloud. When I say know - I have and can build them from scratch - from a chip supplier to programming or creating the toolchain, apps and finally selling it to end customers. My end customers have been &lt;em&gt;PastBigCustomer&lt;/em&gt;, then &lt;em&gt;GovtOfficial1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;GovtOfficial2&lt;/em&gt; - &lt;em&gt;GovtBody1&lt;/em&gt;, Heads of Police, &lt;em&gt;GovtSecurityBody&lt;/em&gt; etc, &lt;em&gt;GovtOfficia3&lt;/em&gt;, heads of state security to mobile manufactures like &lt;em&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;OEM1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;OEM2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt; etc. I influenced the requirements by &lt;em&gt;GovtBody1&lt;/em&gt; on mobile operators that now have made it mandatory for them to provide at least 30 mtr of geolocation accuracy for tracking. Influenced and made them aware that telecom providers are not providing &amp;#8220;real time&amp;#8221; tracking as they are hiding the X interface - &lt;span class="caps"&gt;GSM&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;ref.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways - i ended up telling the customer - &amp;#8220;Sir, I will send you the link to the entire portfolio, Please do call me if you need us. I have more intelligent customers who actually need me&amp;#8221;. I know&amp;#8230;.this was after an hour of humiliation being labeled a data chor (Gargle and I were betraying the country for working there).
10 seconds of silence. He could not believe a &amp;#8220;sales&amp;#8221; ka sirf customer engineer can tell the factual truth to an &amp;#8220;innocent&amp;#8221; person. Then he starts selling &lt;em&gt;AyurvedaMajor1&lt;/em&gt; to us - giving us requirements and all. I am really running late to an yum &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IOT&lt;/span&gt; opportunity - &lt;em&gt;CustomerBigMeterCompany&lt;/em&gt;. I wanted to calm my nerves before that, so this time i am genuinely asking Dear Customer to let me go, he ends up giving us requirements for his immediate &amp;#8220;$$$$$$ requirement&amp;#8221; -  GargleCloud&amp;#8217;s value proposition. &lt;span class="caps"&gt;FSR&lt;/span&gt; and I sync up after call, &lt;span class="caps"&gt;HI5&lt;/span&gt; and conclude that this was an amazing&amp;nbsp;meeting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All pumped up, we have a great opening meeting at &lt;em&gt;CustomerBigMeterCompany&lt;/em&gt; again. Good, hard week&amp;#8230;.this is Friday&amp;#8230;.finally a weekend when I can be proud of the week I had. 10 &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PM&lt;/span&gt;, unusual chat ping from &lt;span class="caps"&gt;FSR&lt;/span&gt;. He/She inquires whether we can talk.
Trivia : I am a father of one 5 year old human, 2 very loving yet annoying dogs and a pseudo father of 40 - 60 street dogs. After 6 &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PM&lt;/span&gt;, my highly stressed wife had given me a notice - money is not enough, you are needed. There was proof to that - my son was not speaking Hindi even at 4 years. Corona time&amp;#8230;.we all struggle with this. I am barely giving time to anyone. My mom passes - i am in Noida, she lives in our old permanent home at rohini, Delhi. I am guilty of not making enough time for her, and probably causing her death&amp;#8230;.i am still coping up with this guilt.
The reason I am telling you this is to simply imply that &lt;span class="caps"&gt;7PM&lt;/span&gt; to 11Pm is an absolute must for me - I have to take over from my wife who is highly stressed being in the final leg of her Phd. She is doing&amp;nbsp;well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyways, Mr &lt;em&gt;CustomerStupid&lt;/em&gt;/&lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor1&lt;/em&gt; , probably after getting drunk at &lt;span class="caps"&gt;10PM&lt;/span&gt; on Friday, gave a call to former &lt;span class="caps"&gt;FSR&lt;/span&gt; and apparently threatened to file a police complaint. I was all for it - It was on web conf, and I thought the version is exaggerated, I tell the &lt;span class="caps"&gt;FSR&lt;/span&gt; to sleep it off, after i finally get done with my day which ends at 11 &lt;span class="caps"&gt;PM&lt;/span&gt; normally - this includes making food for my street dogs - being hated for it, and recently being attacked for it. I hope you saw the video. This is after my moms&amp;#8217;s demise on 28 April, coincidentally the week when &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; joins back from vacation. He is trying to do his thing again - perpetrating general hate against me - my lack of patience, skills and after this meeting 1, even my character for taking a call late at night from a female &lt;span class="caps"&gt;FSR&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Made up Contentious meeting 2 : &lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor2&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;em&gt;PeerLyingUnskilled&lt;/em&gt; lead a disaster of a meeting. &lt;em&gt;PeerLyingUnskilled&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CoworkerSenior1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;PeerAnalyticsSpecialist&lt;/em&gt; are speakers in the meet, i was just a mute spectator.
The meeting goes horribly wrong, time management, content - everything. &lt;em&gt;PeerLyingUnskilled&lt;/em&gt; is panicking and trying to convince me to put blame on &lt;em&gt;PeerAnalyticsSpecialist&lt;/em&gt;, who is a nagler &lt;em&gt;(a new joinee)&lt;/em&gt; at this point. I refuse to intervene and tell her to think about it.
&lt;span class="caps"&gt;BTW&lt;/span&gt;, its the same account where I got &lt;span class="caps"&gt;CIO&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8217;s approval for ######## assessment just a few days back. This is the only reason why we have an edge over competition, and why &lt;em&gt;PartnerImplementor1&lt;/em&gt; has really partnered with us in this account - a fact that &lt;span class="caps"&gt;LT&lt;/span&gt; conveniently forgets to consider.
&lt;em&gt;PeerLyingUnskilled&lt;/em&gt; tells the management that I screwed the meeting up (I was not even allowed to speak in the meet - &lt;em&gt;CoworkerSenior1&lt;/em&gt;/&lt;em&gt;PeerAnalyticsSpecialist&lt;/em&gt; can validate).
I am never asked to clarify or asked what went wrong. (L/T - Blamelessness and &lt;span class="caps"&gt;RCA&lt;/span&gt; is part of &lt;span class="caps"&gt;SRE&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the same time period when I am dealing or rather coping up with implications of my Mothers&amp;#8217; death - the ugly material part of it. Summary - I ended up abandoning all my savings, investments, property to focus on work and move&amp;nbsp;on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Things are going well in other accounts - All the other FSRs seem&amp;nbsp;happy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;18 June, when things were at their decisive time, I was attacked by 3 crazy but quite well built people with Iron rods for 15 mins.
I got my first entitlement of being a gargler - got the days off while I dealt with these all pending&amp;nbsp;issues.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;August 2021
In August, I joined back with a barely functioning hand, trying to handle the piled up work. Got exceptional support from &lt;em&gt;CoworkerGood2&lt;/em&gt;, he created a few deals while I was gone.
I had lost 3 absolutely winnable dials - the FSRs don&amp;#8217;t call me out of respect or sheer self promotional reasons. There were many wins, I was never credited.
Meanwhile, &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt; is going and &lt;em&gt;DimwitManager1&lt;/em&gt; joins, I request &lt;em&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3&lt;/em&gt; to give a true assessment of my progress to enlightened &lt;em&gt;DimwitManager1&lt;/em&gt;, but I am &amp;#8220;hinted informally&amp;#8221; that I am not meeting the&amp;nbsp;OKRs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I give a very detailed and logical lay of the land - progress, key developments and the general good feedback I was getting from customers, partners and even my peers. I am told to prepare 10 account plans as per OKRs, I inform him that these are &amp;#8220;traditional enterprise accounts&amp;#8217; &amp;#8216;, their tech stack cannot be deduced by nmap or any other open source intelligence tools. I inform him about my participation in DevJam and the other bits where I have been helping, but he doesn&amp;#8217;t listen. I tell him about my experience in D/N and my love for gaming and &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IIOT&lt;/span&gt; - power sector&amp;nbsp;etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Power accounts are taken away from me, the regional &lt;span class="caps"&gt;IIOT&lt;/span&gt; lead is a guy who doesn&amp;#8217;t even know &amp;#8220;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;IT&lt;/span&gt;/&lt;span class="caps"&gt;OT&lt;/span&gt;&amp;#8221;. I am left with &lt;em&gt;PeerLiarUnskilled&lt;/em&gt; who has been lying and claiming credit for all my work even till&amp;nbsp;day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now:
I was given &lt;span class="caps"&gt;NI&lt;/span&gt; &lt;em&gt;Needs Improvement&lt;/em&gt;, and contested that, just lost that appeal. My accounts have been ignored - &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR2&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR3&lt;/em&gt; are all big accounts which need a higher level handshake - all of them have been ignored by my local leadership just to continue painting me as&amp;nbsp;incompetent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that is my journey till&amp;nbsp;day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My customers seem to like me more than my management, and they are easier to work with&amp;nbsp;too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CustomerAyurvedaMajor2&lt;/em&gt; deal is on because I pivoted the deal. ################### which finally put the deal on track. &lt;span class="caps"&gt;LT&lt;/span&gt; is going to continue sabotaging my deals in &lt;span class="caps"&gt;BD&lt;/span&gt;- &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR2&lt;/em&gt;, and recently &lt;em&gt;CustomerBD_MAJOR3&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am not a likable person by any means, if you have seen me in meets -  I give it all, and I believe thats what matters - being there for your colleagues and picking up the right priorities.
Yet i am labelled incompetent for simply refusing to &amp;#8220;dance&amp;#8221; as per standards set by luminaries like &lt;em&gt;DimwitManager1&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;ManagerDumbass2&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;ManagerIwantToMatter3&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy new year!&amp;#8230;I am going to make sure that mine makes me grow and&amp;nbsp;evolve.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the best, dealing with all this - I am going to do what I do best - stand up to the bully no matter who and how big they are, and it may get worse&amp;#8230;.I am prepared for&amp;nbsp;that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why it all happened, is something which is going to unravel in next few&amp;nbsp;months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sincerely,&amp;nbsp;Ashish&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Glossary
HasbeenLeader1 : India Head, my skip level, to his credit, he tried a lot to sound smart.
ManagerDimwit1 : My current manager, rattu totta, His extreme loyalty to his Orakle breathren would put a Dogs&amp;#8217; loyalty to shame - Amazing.
ManagerDumbass2 : The last manager, who is sucking up in CanaDDa now, he was tasked with &amp;#8220;taming&amp;#8221; me. Look where we are :)
ManagerIwantToMatter3 : A sidey manager who would provide his useless gyan everywhere. Despite sucking for longer than anyone else and not getting anywhere, he seems optimistic.
moma patch : our internal page
PeerChor : The guy who stole Orakle internal documents and forced me to use them. Part of orakle coterie of of HasbeenLeader1, ManagerIwantToMatter3 and probably&amp;nbsp;ManagerDimwit1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="caps"&gt;PS&lt;/span&gt; : About Macros used,  i may choose to replace these in future with Real Names and Links :)
#### : Readcted&amp;nbsp;Stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="Google"></category><category term="Google"></category><category term="Cloud"></category><category term="Performance"></category><category term="Fairness"></category><category term="ethics"></category></entry></feed>