<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Tech for balance - life</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/feeds/life.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://blog.codeparity.com/</id><updated>2022-05-17T16:02:31+05:30</updated><subtitle>Codeparity Blog</subtitle><entry><title>Status check - 17 May 2022</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/status-update-may2022.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-05-17T15:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-17T15:49:02+05:30</updated><author><name>Codeparity aka Ashish Tanwar</name></author><id>tag:blog.codeparity.com,2022-05-17:/status-update-may2022.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;last 4 months&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Wanted to write this post - started to get a lot of check-ins from people wondering what I have been upto. Most are curious about my mentally health and wellbeing….having chosen to own my reclusive nature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professionally, I am on schedule. Repeating past mistakes is a pattern of insanity, quite aware of the usual. Some things become apparent as you age, for me these have been my priorities in the last 4 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="getting-my-strength-back"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Getting my strength back&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Physical fitness is an absolute necessity in today’s environment. Having a family is a duty, and depending on law enforcement for their safety is absolute stupidity. Blessed to have the best Chief Minister of the country - Yogi Adityanath - that  should not become a reason to become complacent. Law, Police in India are the most pathetic administrative public services in the world…something which won't change in the current scheme of things. Would reason in a separate post.
Hand is better than before now, and the mind/body balance has been restored, though a bigger challenge of creating a sustainable routine remains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="extending-my-reach"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Extending my reach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One’s opportunity and success are highly influenced by the people around them. Being born in  the middle class, I am very much affected by this  bubble or sphere of influence. The last time I launched Codeparity, I counted on the goodwill of the people around me - which did not work out at all. I ended up wasting weeks. Won't happen this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="section" id="realigning-priorities-their-order"&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Realigning, priorities their order&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I left Google in weird circumstances. No matter how I want to ignore this …. One needs time to counter for self bias and get a hold on your reality. Time is invaluable in this exercise. Being an engineer at heart, execution comes easy to me, and that has not really helped things.
With all that done, I am back in the professional sphere again - not as a jobber but as an entrepreneur and investor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you out there. Please follow me on twitter : &lt;a class="reference external" href="https://twitter.com/ashishtanwar"&gt;ashishtanwar&lt;/a&gt;, the wokeness of platforms like linkedin and twitter sickens me, and this is one of the few social/tech issues i would work on in coming months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content><category term="life"></category><category term="life"></category><category term="India"></category><category term="Career"></category><category term="Priorities"></category><category term="Update"></category></entry><entry><title>Applying Maslow's triangle</title><link href="https://blog.codeparity.com/maslaw-needs-heirrarchy-1.html" rel="alternate"></link><published>2022-03-01T01:21:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-05-17T16:02:31+05:30</updated><author><name>Codeparity aka Ashish Tanwar</name></author><id>tag:blog.codeparity.com,2022-03-01:/maslaw-needs-heirrarchy-1.html</id><summary type="html">&lt;p class="first last"&gt;Understanding Maslow's hierarchy of needs&lt;/p&gt;
</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maslow's hierarchy of needs can be useful in understanding an individual, community or a country&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content><category term="life"></category><category term="psychology"></category><category term="analysis"></category><category term="maslow"></category></entry></feed>